In a recent Silicon Catsuit video I've worn this swimsuit underneath when I got undressed
and a lot of you were asking where is this from? It looks so great like liquid metal
and it's from LeoHacks. I'm going to show you today a lot of the new metallic collection
hence the liquid metal name and yeah I thought I'd bring this one again for a quick look
but now I'm going to change into the first one of these.
Alright, this is the basic cut, so to say, long-sleeve swimwear bathing suit
and it is this great liquid metal fabric.
I think there are metallic threads woven into it because if you know when you pet an animal
and in one direction the fur is really smooth and in the other direction it's not smooth.
That's how it feels. I think the look is really really great. I love the shine of the material
and also that it looks like just you mold it out of one piece of solid metal and of course we have
the seams here so it's not really seamless obviously but still they do not
disrupt the full picture and I love it
I also got the matching pants and I'm just going to put it on top here and see
how the full thing looks
all right now it's almost like a catsuit
You can see the seams from the swimsuit underneath here. So that's what I don't like about it. But other than that I think it's a full cool look. Almost seems like the swimsuit is a bit darker than the leggings but that should not be the case.
The leggings is a bit more stretched so maybe that's why it looks a bit different.
Funny thing about the zipper is it's a two way zipper.
You can of course close and open it but you can also open it from below and create something
like a keyhole here.
I think that's really fun.
And also here back side again.
I got this in black too so I'm going to change into that one now.
Alright so this is the same in black.
It is not as shiny.
It's a more subtle shine but I think it's also really nice.
And what I forgot to show you with the silver one.
There's also this bathing suit in silver.
And it may look like not much from the front but the back side is awesome.
I took some pictures with it in my last Thailand holiday, I can show them.
So yeah, I'm not going to wear them now because pictures.
And here we go with the black one.
It's the same zipper and it feels a bit smoother, the fabric, than the silver one maybe because
it's not as metallic shiny and that's why the fabric is a bit different here.
it's also a bit I don't know thinner it's also a bit thinner that's what I was looking for oh my
god and yeah I also have it in white so I'm going to slip into the white one now
and surprisingly the white one I think it's shinier again than the black one
so if you want the real deal then take the silver one and for this one I also have
I also have the matching leggings here
wow now it's white really a lot of white let me adjust the voice band
it's a bit see-through the leggings you can see that here because you can see the
bodysuit in the back and also in the front but the bodysuit itself isn't
see-through so that's a good good point here. The leggings feels a bit rougher but I
think again it's because the fabric is stretched more here than with the
bodysuit. It's really wide but I think the shine is really nice almost like a
mother-of-pearl shine and it looks kind of valuable. I don't know. Okay and one other item I have in white
which I wanted to show you is this bodysuit. So I'm changing again. I love this cut here. I love
the keyhole cutout. I think it is so cool and it's with the short sleeves. You can easily wear it as
a top I have this one in black too and I've worn it as a top a matter of fact when I was in Thailand
again I think these fabrics are really light and really nice to wear so perfect for warm weather
too of course you can also wear them just as swimwear and again I just like the cutout here
and before I end this video I want to show you two other new things from Leo Hex not metallic
collection but I think they're great too but they're a surprise so I'm going to change.
It's a PVC bodysuit and it's the same cup than the very first bodysuit I was wearing in this video
and the new thing about this one is since Leo Hex already has a PVC swimsuit for ages
the contrast stitching here the red and there's also a white PVC swimsuit with
black contrast stitching I was wearing this last week to a pool party where the
dress code was all white and I was lucky to have the leohex items here yeah I
think it's a cool look I've also worn these in the water you can definitely
swim with them I always wash them out with tap water after wearing it to a
swimming pool or the sea so the fabric will last longer but I think they're
really cool and really sporty but also really eye-catching. And the last item
for today is this neoprene swimsuit it's fake neoprene it's not real neoprene
but it looks a lot like neoprene so it's basically fashion neoprene I saw a lot
of neoprene in the last minute and there are new colors available for example
this green there's also like a reddish color so you should definitely check out
your Leo Hex shop for example Amazon and yeah that's all I wanted to show you for
today I think the metallic collection is really really awesome I really like the
silver items because they look just so different from what you usually see out
there so read eye catchers and yeah I think my favorite is also the silver one
but of course the black one is cool because it's black alright leave a
thumbs up and subscribe to my channel here go check out my patreon and leave a
comment and I hope you are going to have a nice day and check out my other Leo
video hacks videos. I've done multiple videos for example on these kind of neoprene swimsuits
and yeah. I guess I'll see you around. Have a nice one. Bye.